{
    "id": "01f8b55a5b1a4013bbef17ebfc941bf3",
    "title": "Gap Fills Exercise",
    "questions": [
        {
            "question": "We ………………………… a party in the afternoon.",
            "description": "The present continuous is commonly used to talk about future events which have already been planned or decided.",
            "answers": [
                "throw",
                "are throwing",
                "would throw"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "Dad ………………………….. for Germany tomorrow.",
            "description": "The present continuous is commonly used to talk about future events which have already been planned or decided.",
            "answers": [
                "leaves",
                "is leaving",
                "leave"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "It ……………………………. later in the day.",
            "description": "We use the simple future to talk about future events which are not already decided.",
            "answers": [
                "rains",
                "will rain",
                "is raining"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "I don’t think that I …………………………. the test.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "pass",
                "will pass",
                "am passing"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "They ……………………………. married in June.",
            "description": "The present continuous is commonly used to talk about future events which have already been planned or decided.",
            "answers": [
                "will get",
                "get",
                "are getting"
            ],
            "correct": 2
        },
        {
            "question": "If they offer a good salary, I ……………………………. that job.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "am accepting",
                "accept",
                "will accept"
            ],
            "correct": 2
        },
        {
            "question": "If they find out, we ………………………………. be in trouble.",
            "description": "In the first conditional, we use a simple present tense in the if-clause and will + first form of the verb in the main clause. ",
            "answers": [
                "will",
                "would",
                "could"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "You …………………………… never succeed.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "will",
                "shall",
                "would"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "I think our team …………………………….. win.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "will",
                "shall",
                "can"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "I …………………………. not allow anyone to read my letters.",
            "description": "Shall and will are common in offers, threats, promises and announcements of decisions.",
            "answers": [
                "would",
                "shall",
                "will"
            ],
            "correct": 2
        },
        {
            "question": "You ……………………………. pay for this.",
            "description": "Shall and will are common in offers, threats, promises and announcements of decisions.",
            "answers": [
                "will",
                "shall",
                "can",
                "would"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "Why did you go swimming in that lake? You …………………………….. yourself.",
            "description": "Could have + past participle is used to criticize people.",
            "answers": [
                "could kill",
                "could have killed",
                "will kill"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        }
    ]
}